A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
- General Assembly Legislation, 1991.
  - Senate Bills, 1991.
    - SB 578 (91) Corporations - Annual registration fees, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - SB 580 (91) Violations of ordinances, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - SB 581 (91) Insurers - Annual statements and reports, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - SB 583 (91) Planning district commissions, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 584 (91) Family and Children's Trust Fund of Virginia, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 587 (91) Land disturbing activities, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 588 (91) Prohibited contracts by state employees or officers, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 589 (91) Local health departments, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 590 (91) Dept. of Economic Development, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 592 (91) Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 593 (91) Registering voters, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - SB 595 (91) Capital and surplus insurer requirements, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - SB 599 (91) Rapid animals, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - SB 602 (91) Change of venue, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - SB 603 (91) Motor vehicle emission inspection, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - SB 605 (91) Local retirement systems, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - SB 606 (91) Licensed nurse practitioners - Prescriptive authority, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - SB 608 (91) Homes for adults - licensure, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 610 (91) Prosecution of misdemeanors, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 613 (91) Animal law violations, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 615 (91) Real estate and tangible personal propert taxes, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 616 (91) Commercial motor vehicles, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 617 (91) Motor vehicle dealers and manufacturers - Warranty obligations, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 620 (91) Public defender offices, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 622 (91) Board for contractors, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - SB 627 (91) Corporations, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - SB 629 (91) Special fund for emergency medical service, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - SB 631 (91) Jail officers and superintendents, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - SB 632 (91) Line of Duty Act, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - SB 635 (91) Dept. of Commerce, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - SB 636 (91) Children conceived by reproductive technologies, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - SB 641 (91) Candidates for election - Notices and filings, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 643 (91) Passenger tramway safety, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 644 (91) Firearms - Reckless handling, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 645 (91) Public retirement systems - Disclosures, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 646 (91) State Corporation Commission, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 647 (91) Corporations - Directors and officers, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 648 (91) Corporate annual reports, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 649 (91) Freedom of Information Act - Electronie communication meetings, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 651 (91) Court disposition of children, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 652 (91) Potomac River Bridge Towing Compact, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 653 (91) Inaugural Committees - Reports, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 654 (91) Virginia Spill Response Council, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 655 (91) Regional cooperative jailing, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - SB 657 (91) Charter - Town of Bluefield, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - SB 658 (91) Circuit Court judges, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - SB 659 (91) Precious metal dealers, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - SB 662 (91) Jail prisoners awaiting trial - Reports, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - SB 664 (91) Retail Franchising Act, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - SB 666 (91) Federally certified airlines and interstate service, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - SB 667 (91) Uniform Commercial Code, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - SB 668 (91) Competitive procurement - Exceptions, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - SB 669 (91) Cut grass, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - SB 670 (91) Reinsurance, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - SB 676 (91) Occupational safety and health standards - Enforcement, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - SB 679 (91) Cemeteries, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - SB 683 (91) State Water Control Board, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 684 (91) Cut grass, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 685 (91) Loaded firearms - Restrictions on access by children, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 686 (91) District Courts, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 687 (91) Subdivision of land, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 691 (91) Sewage disposal systems, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 696 (91) Board for Cosmetology, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 697 (91) Middle schools, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - SB 699 (91) Virginia Transplant Council, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - SB 700 (91) Dept. for the Aging, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - SB 701 (91) Local boards for equalization, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - SB 703 (91) Funeral directors and embalmers, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - SB 705 (91) Employment by school divisions - Criminal record checks, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - SB 706 (91) Persons owing a duty of support, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - SB 708 (91) Solicitations - 900 numbers, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - SB 710 (91) Indentification of evidence, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 713 (91) Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority - Condemnation of cemetery for Dullus expansion, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 715 (91) Dept. of Aviation, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 716 (91) School board petty cash funds, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 717 (91) Tangible personal property - Classifications, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 718 (91) Transportation district trains - Fare evasions, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 720 (91) Disposition of deer causing damage, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 724 (91) Commissioners - Condemnation proceedings, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 725 (91) Medical College of Hampton Roads, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 726 (91) Plastic holding rings, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - SB 728 (91) Bequests to existing trusts, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 730 (91) Paternity - Inheritance, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 731 (91) Fire suppression systems - Local water utility requirements, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 732 (91) Legislative commission on equity and efficiency in public education, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 736 (91) Local license taxes, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 738 (91) Local government regulation of garbage pick-up and disposal - Contracting, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 739 (91) Interest rates - Penalties, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 740 (91) Assessment for solid waste disposal, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 741 (91) Soil scientists, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - SB 743 (91) Meat and poultry inspection, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 748 (91) Uniform Statewide Building Code - Lead based paint levels, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 749 (91) Malpractice review panel, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 750 (91) Medical malpractice, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 751 (91) Extension of regulatory deadlines, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 752 (91) Admission to school - Birth certificate requirement, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 753 (91) School board terms, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 754 (91) Cemetery lots, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 756 (91) Liability - Failure to pay taxes, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 757 (91) Business license requirments, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SB 759 (91) Unexecuted criminal warrants, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 760 (91) Town of Herndon - Automobile Parking Authority, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 761 (91) Election returns and procedures after poll closes, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 762 (91) Motor vehicle insurer - Bad faith failure to pay a claim, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 764 (91) Virginia Consumer Protection Act, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 765 (91) Taxes, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 766 (91) Purchase of handguns, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 770 (91) Excess cost recovery program - Elimination, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SB 772 (91) First offender program, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SB 774 (91) Garbage pick up and disposal, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SB 776 (91) Prohibiting sale of drugs, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SB 777 (91) Local government grievance procedures, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SB 779 (91) Virginia Public School Authority, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SB 782 (91) Collecting and remitting sales and use tax, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SB 784 (91) Bail bonds, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SB 785 (91) Devices to check speed of motor vehicles, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SB 787 (91) Disclosure of an agent moratorium, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SB 790 (91) Capital murder - Penalty, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SB 791 (91) Extension for filing returns and paying taxes, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SB 794 (91) Child support enforcement, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SB 795 (91) Support enforcement, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SB 798 (91) Multi-jurisdictional grang jury, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SB 799 (91) Child support enforcement, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SB 806 (91) Virginia Human Rights Act, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SB 808 (91) Retrieval of hunting dogs, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SB 809 (91) Credit card fraud, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SB 810 (91) Attorney's for the Commonwealth, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SB 817 (91) Local dates for filing returns, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SB 823 (91) Veterans' homes and cemeteries, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SB 833 (91) Parking regulation, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SB 834 (91) Minimum wages, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SB 836 (91) Virginia Retirement System, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SB 837 (91) Subordinate mortgage loans, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SB 838 (91) Collection of delinquent taxes - Administrative fees, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SB 846 (91) Campaign finance reports, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SB 848 (91) Care and control of animals, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SB 857 (91) State income tax payments, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SB 862 (91) State Treasurer, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - SB 864 (91) Sanitation district commissions, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - SB 865 (91) Public schools - Buildin plan approval, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - SB 867 (91) Kindergarten programs, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - SB 869 (91) Family life education materials, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - SB 870 (91) Statewide program to eliminate automobile theft, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - SB 872 (91) Sale of real property - Voidability of contracts, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 877 (91) Waste management facility operators, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 878 (91) Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 879 (91) Compensation Board, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 883 (91) Local departments of social services - Fees, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 884 (91) Boating Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 885 (91) Virginia Korean-Vietnam War History Council, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 887 (91) Birth Related Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - SB 897 (91) Virginia Highway Corporation Act, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - SB 898 (91) Virginia Transportation Contract Revenue Bonds, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - SB 902 (91) Fireworks, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - SB 903 (91) Statewide Cancer Registry, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Special Session I, 1991.
    - HB 3001 (91) Reappointment of House of Delegates districts, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - HB 3001 (91) Reappointment of House of Delegates districts, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - HB 3003 (91) Charter - City of Waynesboro, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HB 3005 (91) Election laws - Definitions, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HB 3006 (91) Condemnation pawers, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HB 3007 (91) Industrial Development Authority - Loudoun Co., 1991. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HB 3008 (91) Virginia Transportation Revenue Bonds, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HB 3009 (91) Unemployment compensation, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HB 3010 (91) Containerized freight - Overweight permits, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - HB 3012 (91) House of Delegates districts, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - HB 3013 (91) Drugs - Penalties, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - HB 3014 (91) Design-Build contracts, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - HB 3015 (91) Elections - Primary and filing schedules, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - HB 3016 (91) House of Delegates districtsd, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - SB 1501 (91) Reapportionment of senatorial districts, 1991. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - SB 1504 (91) Retail sales and use tax exemption, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - SB 1505 (91) Industrial Development Authority - Loudoun Co., 1991. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - SB 1506 (91) Virginia Transportation Revenue Bonds, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - SB 1507 (91) Condemnation power, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - SB 1508 (91) House of Delegates and Senate districts - Written descriptions, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - SB 1510 (91) Reapportionment of senatorial districts, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - SB 1510 (91) Reapportionment of senatorial districts, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Special Session II, 1991.
    - HB 4003 (91) Charter - City of Suffolk, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - HB 4004 (91) Virginia Public Building Authority, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - HB 4005 (91) Boards of supervisors, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - SB 2001 (91) Charter - City of Emporia, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - SB 202 (91) Virginia Public Building Authority, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - SB 2003 (91) Congressional districts, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Legislation arranged by date Approved (House and Senate), 1991.
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Jan 21-Feb 27. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Mar 5-8. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Mar 11-13. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Mar 14-17. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Mar 20. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Mar 20. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Mar 22. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Mar 23-25. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Legislation approved, 1991 Apr 3-30. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Legislation Vetoes / Amended / Reenrolled, 1991.
    - HB 247 (91) Property Owners' Association Act, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - HB 503 (91) Public Finance Act, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - HB 788 (91) Nursning scholarships, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - HB 1150 (91) Public revenues, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - HB 1206 (91) Uniforms in public schools, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - HB 1214 (91) State Corporation Commission - Service of process, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - HB 1233 (91) Inoperable motor vehicles, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - HB 1287 (91) Accrual of actions, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - HB 1293 (91) Investigations of elected officials - Immunity for witnesses, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - HB 1300 (91) Bonus deer permits, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - HB 1379 (91) Issuance of bonds, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - HB 1385 (91) Life insurance - Armed forces and National Guard, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - HB 1400 (91) Surplus property - Sale or lease, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - HB 1407 (91) Design-Build and construction management contracts, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - HB 1454 (91) Literary Funds - Loans, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - HB 1463 (91) Net distances, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - HB 1469 (91) Escheats, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - HB 1472 (91) Advisory Committee on Juvenile Justice, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - HB 1478 (91) Craney Island disposal area, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - HB 1487 (91) Chain of custody - Certificates of analyses as evidence, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - HB 1489 (91) Alterations of vehicles, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - HB 1495 (91) Leaves of absence for employees of the Commonwealth, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - HB 1510 (91) Assessment for courthouse construction, renovation or maintenance, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - HB 1511 (91) Alcoholic Beverage Control laws - Mixed beverages, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - HB 1512 (91) Dept. of Transportation - Civil action, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - HB 1527 (91) Improperly laid venue, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - HB 1528 (91) Tolling of the statute of limitations, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - HB 1530 (91) Child support obligation and provision of health care for dependents, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - HB 1531 (91) Admission to school - Birt certificate requirement, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - HB 1538 (91) Licensing of home care organization, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - HB 1567 (91) Disposition in juvenile courts, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - HB 1606 (91) Interior lights for motor vehicles, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1623 (91) Securities in which fiduciaries may invest, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1626 (91) Multi-jurisdictional grand jury, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1629 (91) Equitable distribution, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1630 (91) Motor vehicle insurance, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1694 (91) Virginia Retirement System - Group insurance program, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1739 (91) Public construction contracts, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1760 (91) Improper closure of pollution control centers, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1770 (91) Authorization of localities to operate stormwater utilities or control programs, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1783 (91) Virginia Real Estate Time-Share Act, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - HB 1735 (91) Underground storage tanks, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - HB 1792 (91) Correction of indexes in clerk's office, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1809 (91) Private operation of corrections facilities, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1824 (91) Virginia Recreational Facilities Authority, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1856 (91) Planning district commissions - Dual membership, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1858 (91) Freedom of Information Act - Executive / closed meetings, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1866 (91) Tuition relief, refund and reinstatement, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1867 (91) Fair Elections Practices Act, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1884 (91) Authorized fines for misdemeanors, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1893 (91) Powers of campus police, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1904 (91) Motor vehicle dealer license plates, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - HB 1881 (91) Driving under the influence - Revocation of licenses, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HB 1898 (91) Speed limits, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HB 1907 (91) Prescription drug refills, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HB 1954 (91) Collection of delinquent taxes - Administration fees, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HB 1956 (91) Business licenses, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HB 1999 (91) Local government regulation of garbage and refuse pick up, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - HB 1940 (91) Commonwealth Transportation Board contracts - Airports, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - HB 1948 (91) State taxes - Erroneous or improper assessments, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - HB 1991 (91) Protective orders, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - HB 1997 (91) Transfer of firearms - Criminal history record checks, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - HB 2000 (91) Motor vehicle safety inspections, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - HB 2005 (91) Virginia Environmental Emergency Response Fund, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - SB 174 (91) Acupunturists, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - SB 283 (91) Child abuse and neglect facilities, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - SB 368 (91) Teaching hospitals - Virginia Personnel Act and retirement plans, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - SB 503 (91) Accrual of actions, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - SB 506 (91) Tax relief for elderly and permanently disabled, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - SB 520 (91) Filling vacancies in the office of the mayor or council, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - SB 524 (91) Retail sales and use tax exemption, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - SB 531 (91) Charter - City of Danville, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - SB 540 (91) Legal possession of illegal drugs, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - SB 579 (91) Penalties for carrying loaded firearms, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - SB 594 (91) Practice of law, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - SB 600 (91) Child support and health care coverage, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - SB 604 (91) Correction of recording index, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - SB 609 (91) Leaves of absence for military duty, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - SB 637 (91) Extended service contracts, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - SB 640 (91) Uniform Statewide Building Code, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - SB 680 (91) Virginia Public Building Authority, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - SB 698 (91) Bingo games and raffles, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - SB 721 (91) Sanitary landfills, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - SB 747 (91) Board for contractors, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - SB 755 (91) Design-Build and construction management contracts, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - SB 775 (91) Design-Build and construction management contracts, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - SB 801 (91) Firearms dealers, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - SB 844 (91) Contractors - Occupational safety and health, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - SB 847 (91) Armed foreces and National Guard - Life insurance, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - SB 852 (91) Counsel in capital cases, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - SB 875 (91) Local recycling and waste disposal, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - SB 895 (91) Aggravated malicious wounding - Penalty, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - SB 900 (91) Commonwealth Transportation Board - Airports, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- General Assembly Legislation, 1992.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1992.
    - HB 1 (92) Animal cruelty offenses, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 3 (92) Relief of Tommy and Darlene Mundy, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 5 (92) Administration of judges - Oaths, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 6 (92) Traffice and pre-payable non-traffic offenses, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 7 (92) Magistrates, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 9 (92) Judges and clerks - Fees on district courts, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 10 (92) Central Criminal Records Exchange, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 11 (92) Exemptions from property tax - Fine Arts Museum of Southern Virginia, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 12 (92) Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 13 (92) Budget process, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 15 (92) Local disability service boards, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - HB 16 (92) Transfer of patient records, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - HB 17 (92) Telephone cooperatives, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - HB 20 (92) Charter - Town of Victoria, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - HB 23 (92) DUI violations, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - HB 25 (92) Preneed funeral contracts, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - HB 29 (92) Charter - Town of Richlands, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - HB 35 (92) Bingo and raffles, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - HB 37 (92) Design build or construction management contracts, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 3)